Mojtaba Namazi Fard

Front-End Developer

DoB: 1998-08-03

Military Service: Served

anf.namazi@gmail.com

(+98)9210886520

(+98)9900890108

anfnamazi.github.io/Resume

Tehran, Iran

Profile Summary

Hi I'm Mojtaba a software engineer with 4 years of experience in developing front-end architectures, current tech stack is: TypeScript, React. Worked with 3 software companies on various project stages: requirements analysis, UI and product design, choosing tech stack, architecture design, and software development. Staying up-to-date with emerging technologies and framework.

Skills



Work Experience

Front-End Developer

Sharif hamrah pazhoohan

Tehran, Iran

March 2019 - Present

Tasks and Achievements

- Participated in the planning and execution of sprints, ensuring timely delivery of high-quality code.
- Implemented performance optimization strategies for adding large amounts of data to the map container.
- Conducted code reviews to maintain code quality and adherence to coding standards.

Front-End Developer

Dade kavan | Andishe bartar

Tehran, Iran

September 2021 - December 2021

Tasks and Achievements

Successfully led the redesign of food ordering process resulting in a 30% increase in user engagement.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Branch: Software

Institute/University: Sadra

Tehran, Iran 2016 - 2020

Language

English: Intermediate

Certificates

React

Institute: Sharif University Free Education

October 2019

Social Network





December 2020 - December 2021 Tasks and Achievements

Front-End Developer

Himart

Tehran, Iran

- Implemented strategies for filtering and sorting shops in near area.
- Optimized web applications for maximum speed and scalability, resulting in a 40% decrease in page load time and a 20% increase in overall site traffic.

